Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream,
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls built between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones we love.
We'll carry on till we see the light.
The sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know.
That's what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Yes, we've got
superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers.
Linlin, you shall pay with your
life for what you have done to Elba.
More similar!
No!
Please stop, Lin-Lin!
You're in!
She's fearful!
Are you okay?
He'll hold her down!
Put out the fire!
Quickly!
Catch that girl already!
We're on it!
Be careful!
Please don't hurt her!
Do you have Simla here?
Yeah, there's some for the
festival in the storehouse.
Then fetch it now. Oh, right.
Mother, what are you
doing? It's dangerous.
Please, just stay back.
I have no choice.
Giver, stop!
I shall give you boys.
Oh, what is that?
Keep my command.
It has a name!
I'm scared.
Is that a demon?
Your name shall be Pandora.
I'll have those some luck!
Hurry! Give it to her!
It's not!
I'm sure you're in the limit!
Blamesimmer!
Your town is no longer ablaze.
But look, the fire!
That's so cute! Hiya, Mother!
She saved us?
A miracle?
I'm sorry, but this is hardly my work.
Rather, we should thank the god of
the sun for showing us compassion.
I'm so happy!
Punisher.
Do not think of that devil as a child.
You must take swift action.
Otherwise she'll surely bring our
people more pain and suffering
Chief Ural.
Call the doctor over
Chief Beardhill.
Forgive me.
You must show her mercy!
You would stop me. Why, Carmel?
This monster has injured Yorul, my
companion of three hundred years.
He's hardly young.
I fear he cannot survive.
A voyage hurt is not decided by how
long they live, but how they meet death.
We must stand on the side of justice.
Anyone who defies Elbeth's
laws cannot be pardoned.
I can sympathize with that.
But whether she's pardoned or not,
Linlin is a mere child who is left
to the House of Lambs like any other.
Please reconsider.
I refuse to abandon this young soul.
What do you suggest then?
I.
Promise to leave this place and
take her far away from here.
You leave us!
But chief beard hill you
gotta punish Lin Lin.
Why should we let her slide when
she's taking everything from us?
What happened to your elbow ride?
So be it.
Remove this demon from my sight at once.
Don't forgive her! Heart!
Stop it!
Let me go!
Wait, what happened to the chief?
He passed away.
She doesn't even remember?
Yorul, the hero of the
giants, has perished.
And by the hands of an unknowingly
destructive child named Linlin.
The gruesome details of that faithful
day, along with word of Carmel's miracle,
quickly spread to the few giant
settlements across the world.
Together with the orphans
from House of Lambs,
who couldn't bear to
be separated from her,
and Charlotte Linden,
now the enemy of all giant kind, Mother
Carmel leaves the shores. of Elbaf.
Seeking to start their lives over,
they relocate and build a
brand new House of Lambs.
Phew, finally done.
How does it look?
It's lovely.
I apologize once again for
asking so much of you all.
We're pretty deep in the mountains.
Without your assistance, I never would
have been able to build a house like this.
Don't mention it.
If it means we'll never see
Lin-Lin again, it's worthwhile.
Anyway, you're the holy
mother to us giants, too.
Don't forget, we're
always happy to help you.
Much appreciated.
Hoping to put the nervous
children at ease, Mother Carmel?
Smiled
warmly
within
only a few days,
things are starting to feel
like how they used to be.
A
house of lambs is once again
filled with children's laughter.
Look after the place while I'm away;
I'll make sure to scrub the bathroom.
I can do the laundry.
You won't be gone too long, will you?
I'll head straight home as soon
as I'm done buying the groceries.
Is there anything in
particular that you'd like?
Very shortcake, a deck of
cards, some toy samurai swords.
I think I got it all.
Bye!
Word of the House of Lambs
reached round the world.
Gaining a reputation for welcoming and
rehabilitating the most troubled children,
it's a place well respected by all.
I was worried you wouldn't show up.
Give me some credit.
And the entire time we've known each
other, have I ever stood you up once?
Now, how about we get
down to business already?
I have got something big.
I never expected you to leave, Elbaf.
I had to.
I really didn't want to give this one up.
Just consider it.
Five years old and has
the power to destroy
half of a giant's village all by herself.
But the asking price...
Certainly, that's pocket change for you.
Toss her in the Navy and she could be
a vice-admiral or even fleet-admiral.
In Cypherpoll, she'd be a coveted
shield for the Celestial Dragons.
I've been trafficking kids for 50 years.
I have never seen a product
as resilient as this one.
Remember that stunt we
pulled 37 years back
that got me inside Elbaf
in the first place?
You have me to thank for John Giant,
the first of their kind
to ever serve as a marine.
It was all because of my connections.
need i remind you i have been running
this operation for ages without
the children knowing and consistently
you have gotten a new batch
from me every other year orphans
make the best spies don't they no
family no strings attached all right
all right i'll get you the money
damn straight you will it
ain't easy acting as the
holy mother because of
that i was kicking around
the idea of leaving the old biz after this
transaction this is my last
big score so you're gonna
need to pay up money
bags what are you all in
the mood to sing today
kids this is rude oh yeah
but that's a pirate song
though you betcha we're
gonna sail the sea someday
really that does sound
You brats will hit the seas all right,
after you're sold off to the government.
I hope you're ready!
Surprise!
We want to wish you a
happy birthday, Lidlund!
Thanks so much, everybody!
We know how much you love Semla,
so we made a bunch and piled them into
this big old croquembouche just for you!
We hope you like it!
I've never had Krieg Beach before!
Looks tasty!
Start the tea party!
The tea party?
You're gonna love, I promise!
We all get together and gather
around the table, sipping tea,
eating desserts, and making memories.
That sounds cool! Let's do it! Hooray!
We'll make some tea!
Join us, Mother!
Be right there!
Oh, thank you! Yay!
Dig in, birthday girl!
Go on, eat up!
Please help yourself!
Okay, here I go!
That is yummy!
She eats so fast!
I've never had so much fun!
I don't want this!
This is so good!
One day, Mother Carmel
mysteriously vanished.
And it happened on the
day that Lin-Lin had
the happiest birthday
ever in her entire life.
She was surrounded by her dear friends
and fellow orphans at the House of Lambs,
along with her beloved,
kind-hearted Mother Carmel.
Embraced by all those smiles while
eating her delicious birthday dessert,
Lin-Lin was unable to hold
back her cries of gratitude.
These are all for you, so enjoy!
I'm so happy you guys are the best!
What a picture-perfect day it was.
She couldn't even see
through her own tears.
Slow it down, they aren't
going anywhere, you know.
I'm so glad she likes the dessert we made.
It's your special day!
There's plenty left.
We should do this again every year.
Who the heck needs family when
we have each other? I agree.
It's so sweet.
What a truly wonderful birthday.
That was so good.
I ate so much, I even took
a bite out of the table.
Whoopsie.
Thanks a ton, everybody.
Hey buddy, I'll never
ever forget about today!
Huh?
You guys?
Mother?
Mother Carmel did not answer.
Where did you go?
And her friends were
nowhere to be found. Hello?
Where are you?
Hey, are you inside?
Hey!
Where are you?
It's Lipplin!
So that's where you guys were, huh?
Come back, please don't leave me alone.
Oh, I wonder where everyone could be.
Hey, Mother, why did you
suddenly vanish on me?
Where did you go that day, dear Mother?
It was 63 years ago when
Mother Carmel and the
orphans from the House
of Lambs went missing.
Even Big Mom herself doesn't
know the fate they suffered.
However, there were two people
present that day who do.
Where did you go?
The first being a
warrior of Elbaf who came
to check in on how the
children were adapting.
Monster!
Turning pale, the giant took
off without ever looking back.
He never returned to that island again.
Eventually,
the horrific tale spread through Albath
and then to the other giant villages.
It was from that day forward
that Charlotte Linlin became so
despised among their people that
they were loath to speak her name,
as if it were a curse.
Where did you go?
No! Mother! Everyone!
There was only one other
witness to that horrific scene.
He was a failed cook and former pirate,
also living on the same
island, by the name of Struzan.
He found the gruesome incident amusing.
Thanks to the power of the kuk-kuk fruit,
this man has the ability to
turn any object into food.
That little monster, how interesting.
Please come back!
I don't want to be alone!
It would be a waste if I
just let her die out here.
Where are you, Mother?
You'll work up an appetite
if you keep crying.
What could be the matter?
Come on, dry those eyes.
Tell me, little lady, what are
your future dreams and aspirations?
Hey, what are you?
Let's keep our distance.
Have you seen my mother?
She was just here.
I don't know where all
my friends could be.
Don't have a clue, but I bet they'll
all return here before you know it.
You think so?
Just stick with me while you wait.
I don't mean to brag, but I'm a fine cook.
I'll make sure you're
well-fed until they come back.
I am pretty hungry.
Here, watch what I can do.
This fateful encounter led to the
eventual start of the Big Mom Pirates,
who have only grown in numbers since.
Lin-Lin!
Come to your senses!
They're going to shoot you!
So, at the tea party today,
What do you suppose will happen?
when we smash that picture to pieces?
Mama will be in utter shock
and we'll get at least five
seconds where everyone will
be paralyzed from her cry.
Then it's the KX Launcher's time to shine
and the world will have one less Emperor.
It's over. You all back.
Mama!
Mother, why is everyone trying to stop me?
A perfect world would be where
everyone lives happily as equals.
And yet,
you've probably never heard of a land
where all races live together peacefully,
right?
So, I say, let's make that place here.
The first country where everyone can
get along with one another. Really?
Uh-huh.
Let's create a home
without racism or bias.
One where everyone can
see things eye to eye.
See eye to eye.
How lovely!
So that everyone will get big like me!
Wow!
Now we can all play
without you getting hurt!
Yeah! Sounds great! Right, guys?
Let's do it!
You bet!
I'm happy you're all in.
Now let's work towards
that dream, shall we?
Count me in! Me too! Me too! Yeah!
Let's make this place into a dreamland!
I'll work extra hard too, Mother.
You're such a sweet girl, thank you.
If only all the other countries
could think like this,
I believe the world would
truly be a peaceful place.
And in turn, everyone could
live their lives happily.
I thought we were all going to be happy.
Why did it come to this?
I see.
So is world peace your
dream then? How nice.
That's what I want.
I'm going to make a land
that Mother would like.
I'll figure out a way.
Don't cry.
There's no need to be sad.
There is, though.
I want to see Mother's magic
right now. Magic? Uh-huh.
She's special.
She plays with us in a fun way.
I'll pretend.
I'm Mother, okay? Watch.
She put her hands like this.
Flower, flower, flower, flower, flower.
And that's the spell she
used to cast. That's cool!
Did I do that?
What the hell?
Could it be a Devil Fruit?
Oh, I can do it too now, Homer!
Thanks so much, Lin-Lin!
Let's all sing together!
Okay, that settles it.
I'm taking her out to sea with me.
This is so exciting!
Oh, that dream you mentioned!
I might be able to help.
You want everyone to see eye to eye? No!
Come on, Lin-Lin!
Let's make that country.
We'll start today.
Would you like that? Yes?
Look, you guys see this?
I can't believe it.
A 50 million bounty?
For a kid?
How is that even possible?
You're telling me that a little
girl destroyed the castle?
That ain't a little girl.
It's a monster.
Cypherpole warned us to
approach with extreme caution.
That girl will be
troubled when she's older.
Caesar, let's go! Sure!
That's her! Come on!
Hey, Lin-Lin, company!
I'm eating my sweets!
Go! The GPS!
Almost overnight, Charlotte
Linden became a global threat.
She stomped down a path
to destruction wreaking
havoc everywhere she
and Strewson traveled.
Paparazzi!
Roar!
Bring me your finest confectionaries!
Your Majesty!
On hand, our King!
Don't you want to live
in a country of peace?
Then fetch my dessert.
I'll make sure everyone's happy.
As long as you obey.
If they don't want to get along,
they're just being selfish.
So I'll have to kill them.
Mother, I miss you.
I miss you.
Mother.
then we'll all sit at the
same table again but there
are still some people who
are not listening to me
and now i'm so sad i can't
stop crying all i have is
one cherished photo of you
mother What a good girl.
They took it away from me.
They destroyed the only
memento I have left of you.
Unforgivable.
Unforgivable!
How dare the Straw Hats do this?
Oh, my God!
Ah! Crap!
That's an issue!
Run away!
Did they goof it up?
use your brain since i can fly i'll dive
onto the scene with a
mirror to create an easy
escape route for everyone
soon as you finish
your dirty words dive
right into season's mirror
i still gotta see my job through damn it i
can't believe that destructive hair ruined
my beautiful invention i guess that's what
we get for messing with
an emperor of the sea
Time to end, Scrape boys,
bum rush the mirror!
Ah-ha!
What incredible wind pressure!
Rats!
We're stuck on the roof,
with nowhere to bail!
And we can't win this fight!
It's full-scale rook time, boys!
Oh, my God.
The Big Father.
Oh man, that's cool!